Aaron Ziegelman Foundation collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 4: Moving images
  - #10, AFC 2003/002: MV291; VHSC Maxell
  - Kaminskii #9, AFC 2003/002: MV292; VHSC Maxell
  - Cymerbojm #3, AFC 2003/002: MV293; VHSC Maxell
  - Satsuk, Petro, AFC 2003/002: MV294; VHSC Maxell
  - Cymerbojm #9, AFC 2003/002: MV295; VHSC Maxell
  - Cymerbojm #8, AFC 2003/002: MV296; VHSC Maxell
- Series 5: Electronic media
  There are 31 3 1/2 inch floppy disks 4 zip disks and 2 CDs. They represent the working files for the Luboml Exhibit.
- Series 6: Artifacts
  - Menorah pieces (3) and Candlestick (1) (Box 72)
  - Autograph Album (1) Wood and Brass Shoe Tool (1) Wood Art Frame (2) (Box 73)
  - Drawn Work Pillow cover (2) (Box 74)
  - Embroidered Blouse (Box 75)
  - Embroidered Pillow (Box 76)
  - T’IFILIN (2) (Box 77)
  - Tea towel (1), T’IFILIN BAGS (2) (Box 78)
  - Embroidered Shawl (1) (Box 79)
  - Nazi-era Directional sign (1) Brick Fragment (1) (Box 80)
  - Ukranian doll (Box 81)
  - Engraved silver lid (with Hebrew writing): A32.2, Two pronged silver fork: A32.3 (Box 82)
- Series 7: Published materials
  - Kagan, Berl. 1997. Luboml: The Memorial Book of a Vanished Shtetl. Tel Aviv: Ktav, 1 book (Box 83)
    Includes a list of signatures including the creators of the Luboml Exhibition Project, Fred Wasserman and Aaron Ziegelman. There is also a signature of James Billington, Librarian of Congress.
    Non-archival copies of the book are available in the Library collections: https://lccn.loc.gov/97006197
  - 1997. Luboml: A Small Jewish World. Jerusalem: Yad Vashem, 1 exhibit catalog
    The catalog to the Luboml Exhibit Project, written in English and Polish. Provides a brief history of Luboml prior to World War II.
  - 1999. The Reconstructionist Rabbinical College honors Aaron Ziegelman and presents the New Tamid Award to CLAL, The Reconstructionist Rabbinical College Tribune Journal, 1 event booklet
    Booklet dedicated to Aaron Ziegelman's work within the Jewish communty as well as his work with the Luboml Exhibition Project. Included in the booklet are reproduced letters from various dignatories including President of the United States of America, Bill Clinton and Vice President, Al Gore. In English.
  - Living Memorial to the Holocaust--Museum of Jewish Heritage. 1995. Generation to Generation. New York, 1 booklet
    The booklet honors the sponsors of the Museum of Jewish Heritage which was under contruction at the time of the dinner.
  - Modrzejewska, Beata. 2002. Exhibition of Memories, KaleidOscOpe: 66, 1 magazine
    Article highlighting the Luboml Exhibition Project, along with an interview with Aaron Ziegelman. In English and Polish.
  - Luboml Exhibition Project. 1996. Remembering Libivne: The Jewish Community of Luboml, 1 booklet
    A guide to the items in the collection. Updated revised version, October 1996. In English.
  - Luboml Exhibition Project. Remembering Libivne: The Jewish Community of Luboml, 1 book
    Older version.
  - 1988. POBEHƜͶA. Kiev: Mystetstvo, 1 book
    Rovno region pictorial works. In Ukrainian. Mila Mashkovska wrote a few words thanking Fred Wasserman, September 13, 1995.
  - 1986. BOԒͶΗЬ. Kiev: Mystetstvo, 1 book
    Pictorial works. In Ukrainian. A few words are written on the inside of the book in Ukrainian, October 10, 1995.
  - Ukrainian Telephone Directory, 1 book
    A copy of a telephone directory from Luboml. In Polish. It is signed copy from Petro Yushehuk to Aaron Ziegelman, August 10, 1995.